（アラジン）はぁ　はぁ　はぁ…。
（村人）おい！
（村人）ババ様！
Elder Baba!
ババ様　しっかりしろ！
ババ様！
Hang on!
Elder Baba!
おばあちゃん！
まだ生きてる。→
Granny!
She's still breathing!
We need to get her back to the village immediately!
早く　村へ運ぶんだ！
≪あっ…　ああ！
G-Got it!
I'll carry her.
僕が運ぶ。
You can't die, Granny!
（心の声）
≪死なないで　おばあちゃん≫
♪♪～
akogare wo ima tsukanda
My desires are within reach.
daikansei no namari ni
If the loud, welcoming cheers
kokochiyoku utaretanara
shoot home straight into your heart,
saa tobikomou
then come and jump in!
♪♪～
ashita kara umare kawaru toka
People say they'll change the next day.
dareka ga mikiri tsuketa toka
But they give up so easily.
kono machi no style toka
That's just how it is here.
sonna mono ni nagasare tsuzukete
They get swept away by those excuses day by day.
kado no toreta genseki ni ha
They're nothing more than a chip, swept off the edge
kitto daremo you ha nai
and no longer needed by anyone.
♪♪～
fushigi to tobira no mukou ni ha
Guess what? Out there,
v.i.p nanoru yatsu ha naku
no one's swaggering around like a VIP.
daremo ga kunou no hate sa ore mo
Everyone suffers their own heartaches, myself included.
akogare wo ima tsukanda
But my desires are within reach.
♪♪～
mi wo yudanereba ii  kaji ha kono te ni
Throw yourself in with abandon. I've got the wheel.
mitsu kazoete the show time
On the count of three, it's show time!
daikansei no namari ni
If the loud, welcoming cheers
kokochiyoku utaretanara
shoot home straight into your heart,
saa tobikomou
then come and jump in!
♪♪～
5th Night
Dungeon Capturer
（白瑛）本当ですか？
はい。
Is that true?
Yes. He appears to have been attacked by the Kouga clan while on patrol.
警備中に　黄牙一族の急襲を
受けたもようです。
（呂斎）
だから　申し上げたでしょう。→
As I said,
there is no need to negotiate any longer with people like them.
もはや
交渉など不要。
ひと思いに
殲滅すべきです。
We should destroy them all at once.
I will head to the Kouga village.
黄牙の村へ　向かいます。
（呂斎）なっ…。
Wha-
本当に
我が軍に対して　矢を向けたのか→
I must confirm whether they really
turned their arrows on our army or not.
確かめねばなりません。
バン！
（呂斎）勝手は　許しませんぞ！→
I will not put up with your whims any longer!
You may be a princess, but you're the daughter of the previous emperor.
あなたは
姫君とはいえ　前皇帝の娘。→
Your standing now is only due to the benevolence of our current emperor.
今の地位は　現皇帝陛下の
ご慈悲で与えられたもの。
And His Majesty has put your safety in my hands.
そして　私は　陛下より→
あなたの監視を任されている。
I cannot permit your foolish actions.
勝手な行動は　見逃せませんな。
（白瑛）
ならば　私個人として向かいます。
Then I shall go there not as a princess, but as an individual.
（呂斎）白瑛殿。
Princess Hakuei...
To force obedience by the sword now will only invite bloody rebellion later.
武力による支配は　いずれ→
大きな復讐を招く。
The only way to truly sway a person's loyalty is through noble goals and intentions.
真に　人の心をつかむもの→
それは　崇高な理想と志のはずよ。
はぁ…　もはや　止めません。
I give up. I won't stop you.
が　留守中の軍の指揮権は
私が預かる→
But you must leave me in charge of the troops in your absence.
Does that sound fair?
それで　よいですかな？
I have no choice.
（白瑛）やむをえません。
行きますよ　青舜。
We are going, Seishun.
（青舜）はい。
Yes.
ババ様を射た矢は
煌帝国のそれと同じだ！
The arrow that struck Elder Baba belongs to the Kou Empire!
（一同）えっ？
戦うべきだ！
We must fight back!
奴隷狩りされ
ババ様を闇討ちされ→
They stole our women and they ambushed Elder Baba!
もう我慢する理由は
どこにもない！
There's no reason to hold back anymore!
ああ～　そうだ！
一族の未来のために　戦うべきだ！
Yeah!
For the sake of our clan, we must fight!
≪そうだ　そうだ！
≫そうだ～！
Yeah!
Wait!
（ドルジ）待てよ　みんな！　ババ様は→
Elder Baba said that we can't allow it to come to war, no matter what happens.
何があっても
戦争はしてはいけないと言った。→
ただ生きるための
心の戦をすべきだと…。
She asked us to wage a war in our hearts for survival!
相手に　そんなつもりはないんだ。
Yeah, like the enemy's going to do that!
トーヤたちだって
奴隷にされかけたんだ。→
Touya and the other girls were almost forced into slavery!
We have no choice but to fight!
もう戦うしかない！
（トーヤ）あぁ…。
（ドルジ）あっ…。
≫やっちまえ～！
≫（村人）おお～！
≫（村人）やるぞ～！
おばあちゃん…→
Granny...
Your beloved village is in trouble, Granny.
おばあちゃんの大好きな村が
大変だよ。
（村人）
戦うんだ　一族の誇りのために！
For the pride of the clan,
we will fight!
（村人）一族のために～！
（一同）おお～！
For our clan!
♪♪～
What should I do?
どうしよう…
みんなが死んじゃう。
Everyone will die...
（ババ）力を貸しておくれ　アラジン。
Please lend me your strength, Aladdin.
あっ…　あっ！
Kou
（隊員）これで
全権を掌握できたわけですね。→
And just like that, full command over the troops is yours.
しかし　あれだけ挑発したのに
兵一人　殺さぬとは→
I can't believe those Kouga...
Even after all we did, those cowards
failed to kill a single one of our men.
とんだ腰抜けですな。
おかげで　こちらが→
Thanks to their spinelessness, we had to do the dirty work.
手を汚すはめになりました。
（呂斎）ふん。→
I wonder what will happen now when our
princess wanders carelessly into their territory.
しかし　そこへ　我らの姫様が
のこのこと現れたら→
どうなるであろう。
（隊員）と…　言いますと？
What do you mean?
I'm just worried.
私は　心配しておるのだよ。
Our princess is about to waltz into an angry clan.
怒り狂った異民族に　姫様が→
I don't want to be a downer, but I'm worried she might get herself killed.
万が一にも
討ち取られやしないかとね。
ふっ。
Wa-Was that your plan all along?
ま…　まさか
そのために　すべてを？
But why?
一体　なぜ…。
（呂斎）なぜ？
Why?
Because I just can't get enough of it.
好きだからさ。→
I love watching those peace-loving fools turn red with anger,
口では　戦が嫌いだとか
ぬかしていたバカどもが→
怒り狂い
本性を　むき出しにして殺し合う→
show their true colors, and rip each other apart like animals.
戦争がね。
Because I love war.
I cannot believe that the Kouga clan would wish to start a war.
（白瑛）黄牙の一族が
戦を起こしたがっているとは→
思えません。
（青舜）なぜです？
Why not?
Because of what that strange young man said to me.
昨晩　不思議な少年から
話を聞いたからです。
Granny and the others taught me the meaning of family. They're very important to me.
（回想）((僕に　家族を教えてくれた
大好きな人たちなんだ))
((殺さないで))
Don't kill them.
Is that boy a Dungeon Capturer?
（青舜）その少年
迷宮攻略者なんでしょうか？
I do not know.
分からない。　でも　彼の言葉は
信用できる気がしました。
But I felt that I could trust him.
（青舜）姫様と　何か
通じ合ったのかもしれませんね→
Maybe you two were able to connect on a deeper level
同じ攻略者として。
as kindred Dungeon Capturers!
♪♪～
（白瑛）
とにかく　話し合いましょう。
At any rate, let us go speak with them!
♪♪～
ヒヒーン！（馬の鳴き声）
うっ…　うわっ！
（青舜）あっ！
♪♪～
姫様。
Princess!
よくも　ババ様を！
（白瑛）落ち着いてください。→
How dare you guys shoot Elder Baba!
Please calm down.
We have come only to talk.
我々は　交渉をしに参ったのです。
ふざけるな！→
Don't lie to us!
We won't fall for your tricks anymore!
もう　だまされないぞ！
姫様！
Princess!
でやぁ～！
（村人）なんで　よけない？
Why didn't you move?
We have no desire to fight.
（白瑛）我々に　戦意はありません。
Please allow us the privilege of a discussion. We only wish to ascertain the truth.
真相を探るためにも
交渉の席を　どうか。
（一同）あっ…。
≪（村人）だまされるな！→
Don't let her fool you!
She said the same thing yesterday!
昨日と同じ手だ。　やっちまえ！
そ…　そうだ！
Get her!
Y-Yeah!
Stop, you fools!
（ババ）やめんか　バカども！
（一同）あっ！
Elder Baba!
（村人）ババ様！
How could you act so shamefully? And
you dare to call yourself Kouga warriors?
情けないまねをするな。
それでも　黄牙の戦士か！→
Do not lose sight of what truly must be protected.
見誤るな
己が　本当に守るべきものを。
And do not forget how to fight that battle!
そのために
どんな戦い方をすべきかを！
（一同）あっ…。
♪♪～
The Kouga shall accept the jurisdiction of the Kou Empire.
我が一族は
煌帝国の傘下に下ります。
Elder Baba!
ババ様！
あんなヤツらに下ったら→
If do that, they'll kill us all!
皆殺しにされてしまいます！
（ババ）ご覧のとおりです　姫様。→
It is at you see, Princess.
Our clan has long suffered invasions and slave hunters,
我が一族は
長きにわたる侵略と奴隷狩りで→
心身ともに
傷つき果てております。→
and we bear those scars in our minds and on our bodies.
I will not allow any more of my family to be harmed.
私は　これ以上
家族が　傷つくのを許せません。→
一度は　御国と戦うことさえ
覚悟しておりましたが→
At one time, I was prepared to war with your people.
But then a child said to me,
しかし
ある子供が　私に言うのです。→
"Their leader is someone you can trust."
敵国の将たるあなたは
信用できる人物じゃと。
♪♪～
But that wound is not one you can get from regular day-to-day activities.
しかし
その傷は　尋常ではありません。→
やはり　我が軍の矢で…。
My troops must have been the ones to-
It is life of a village leader compared to the lives of her whole village.
村長一人と　村人全員の命→
You know which one holds more importance.
どちらが大事か
あなたなら分かろう。
♪♪～
I have understood your wishes and take them on as my own.
（白瑛）あなたの意思
確かに　受け継ぎました。→
From this day forward, the safety and
security of the Kouga clan is guaranteed,
これより　黄牙一族は
煌帝国および白瑛の名のもとに→
under the name of the Kou Empire and my own, Hakuei.
安全を保障します。
ついに　他国に下るのか…。
And just like that, we're people of the Kou Empire.
（ドルジ）関係ないだろ　そんなこと。→
What does that matter?
As long as we keep our pride strong in our hearts, nothing has changed.
誇り高い心を
持ち続ければいいだけだ→
ババ様のように！
We must be like Elder Baba!
What is your answer, people of Kouga?
（ババ）どうじゃ　黄牙の者たちよ！→
己が意思を示せよ！
Show us what you wish for!
♪♪～
Isn't this amazing, Ugo?
≪すごいね　ウーゴくん≫
They all have the courage to choose what steps they must take to guarantee their future.
≪みんな
未来のために　何をすべきか→
選ぶ勇気を持ってる≫
We didn't have to do anything.
≪僕らには
何も　すべきことがなかったよ≫
（ドルジ）ババ様　しっかり！
Elder Baba!
Hang in there!
（トーヤ）おばあちゃん！
（ドルジ）ババ様！
Granny!
Elder Baba!
What's the matter, Aladdin?
≪（ババ）どうした？　アラジン。
あっ！
こんな後ろで　一人でいてからに。
What are you doing back here all alone?
Granny... You died.
おばあちゃん
死んじゃったんだね。
Everyone's crying.
みんな　泣いてるよ。
おばあちゃんのこと→
They all loved you.
大好きだったんだね。
（ババ）ほっほっほっほっ。→
You speak as though you are not one of them.
ひと事のように言いなさる。→
What about you, Aladdin?
アラジンは　どうなんだい？
I love you too, Granny.
僕だって
おばあちゃんのこと大好きさ。
But my memories with you are less than theirs.
でも　僕は　みんなより
思い出が少ないからね。
Oh Aladdin. You think of yourself as alone in the world, don't you?
のう　アラジン。
お主　自分が独りぼっちだと→
思っておるじゃろう？
えっ？
そんなことはないよ。
あっ…。
But that's not true.
（ババ）
この姿になった今　わしは　やっと→
Now that I am in this form, I have
finally understood who you really are.
お主のことが　分かったんじゃ。→
あれを　ご覧。
えっ？
Take a look over there.
くっ…　ああ～！
あっ！
All living things in this world are individuals,
（ババ）生きとし生ける者は個→
しかし　その源泉は→
yet the source of their lives is singular.
すべて　一つに集約される。→
That is rukh, the lifeblood of this earth, made up of all of our souls.
すべての魂をつなぐ世界の血潮→
それが　ルフ。
そして　そのルフに愛され→
And you, the one who is loved by the rukh and able to borrow its power,
力を
借りることができるお主は…→
are a Magi.
お主は　マギ。
幾億の生命と共に生き→
One who lives with the souls of countless millions,
彼らを導いて　世界を創る者。
who guides them, and who creates their world.
That's why you are never alone.
だから
お主は　独りではないんだよ。
あっ！
♪♪～
あっ…。
（ババ）愛しいソロモンの子よ→
Beloved child of Solomon,
I will always be by your side.
いつも　味方でいるよ。
ピィ　ピィ　ピィ　ピィ…（ルフの声）
From now on, we must protect the peace of this land.
（白瑛）これから　この地の平和を
守らねばなりません。
（青舜）はい。
そして　戻ったら→
Yes.
And when we return, there is something I must take care of.
片づけなければならないことが
あります。
♪♪～
What do you think you're doing?
何をするつもり!?
（呂斎）何って　戦争ですよ。
Obviously, going to war!
兵を退きなさい！→
Call back the troops now!
The Kouga clan has come under our rule peacefully as a result of negotiation.
黄牙の村は
交渉により　傘下に収めました！
（呂斎）ふん！
期待外れの腰抜けでしたな。→
They're even bigger cowards than I thought.
They willingly accepted your negotiations even after
being captured for slavery and attacked during the night.
奴隷狩りされ
闇討ちされたのにもかかわらず→
唯々諾々と
交渉に　応じてしまうとは。
やはり　あなただったのね　呂斎。
So it was your doing, Ryosai!
そうですよ。
ただし　私の筋書きは　こうでした。
Yes, it was. But my version of the story goes like this:
異民族の村で
姫は　哀れにも惨殺されてしまう。
Sadly, the princess was brutally murdered by the Kouga clan.
残された呂斎は　姫の敵討ちに→
Seeking revenge for the princess, Ryosai led
the entire army to destroy the Kouga village.
全軍を率いて　村を滅ぼすとね。
さあ　どうかしらね。
千人長の　あなたごときが→
Is that how you see this?
You think someone like you, with only a
thousand retainers, can lead a whole army?
全軍の指揮を？
くっ！
（白瑛）なぜ　そんな不相応なことを
考えてしまったのかしら？
How did you come up with such a preposterous idea?
お前さえ来なければ　この私が
抜擢されるはずだったのだ→
If only you hadn't appeared, I would've been the one selected!
I would've been the general of this army!
この部隊の将にな！→
こいつらは　私直属の部下。→
These men are my direct underlings.
Shut up and die, you bitch!
安心して　くたばれ　クソ女！
♪♪～
ふん！
（呂斎）怪しげな技を…。→
These tricks!
迷宮攻略者め。　討ち取れ～！
You blasted dungeon capturer!
Kill her!
（一同）わあ～！
くっ！
眷属器　双月剣！
Household Vessel: Double Moon Swords!
（一同）うわ～！
What are your orders?
いかがいたしましょう？
時間を稼いで。
Buy me time.
この程度の兵力なら
残りの魔力で蹴散らせます。
What power I have left over should be enough to deal with riffraff like them.
了解！
Understood!
Spirit of maniacal love and chaos, I command thee!
（白瑛）
狭愛と混沌の精霊よ　汝に命ず。→
Cover my form, live in my frame,
我が身を覆え→
我が身に宿れ
我が身を　大いなる魔人と化せ。
change me into a great magician!
Paimon!
パイモン！
♪♪～
Traitor Ryosai.
（白瑛）逆賊　呂斎。→
The first princess of the Kou Empire,
煌帝国第一皇女→
練白瑛が　刑に処す。
Hakuei Ren, sentences you to death!
Prepare yourself!
覚悟せよ！
（トーヤ）ババ様　おやすみなさい。→
Rest in peace, Elder Baba.
うぅ…　ううっ…。
ウーゴくん
僕は　この村に来てよかったよ。
I'm glad I came to this village, Ugo.
I've finally learned what I am.
自分のことが
やっと分かってきた…→
Or at least, part of it.
そんな気がするんだ。
あのとき
君が言ってたとおりだね。
It's just as you said back then.
ピィ　ピィ　ピィ　ピィ…
なんだろう？
I wonder what's going on?
（一同）うわ～！
At this rate, we'll be destroyed!
このままでは　全滅です！
（呂斎）矢を放て！
Fire your arrows!
We will hit our own men by accident!
味方に当たります。
案ずるな→
Don't worry, you won't.
当たりはせん。　矢を放て～！
Shoot now!
♪♪～
はぁ…。　このままでは
魔力がもたない。　青舜！
If it keeps going on like this, I'm going to run out of power.
Seishun!
（青舜）はい！
Coming!
We will finish this in one go!
（白瑛）一気に　かたをつけます。
♪♪～
（白瑛）「マグルアルハザード」！
Magul Alhazad!
うっ…　うわ～！
♪♪～
姫様。
呂斎を…。→
Princess!
Where is Ryosai?
We've weakened the enemy forces.
敵の数は　減らした。
呂斎を捕らえよ。
Capture Ryosai!
（呂斎）
なんの数を減らしたのですかな？
What forces might you be referring to?
♪♪～
（白瑛）うっ！
Once the magic stored in the Metal Vessels is used up,
（呂斎）金属器にためた魔力を
使いきれば→
その恩恵を受ける眷属器は
何もできなくなる。→
the connected Household Vessels are useless.
無力ですなぁ　攻略者殿。
You're powerless now, aren't you, little miss Dungeon Capturer?
くっ！
（呂斎）安心なさい　姫様。→
Don't fret, Princess.
すぐに　殺してさしあげますよ。
あなたの大事な弟→
I will kill you quickly.
And I'll kill your precious little brother, Hakuryuu Ren, too!
練白龍もね。
ぐっ！
You bastard!
貴様～～!!
ガキン！
Yes, come at me. I am also a warrior.
いいでしょう。　私も武人…
どちらが　将軍にふさわしいか→
Let's have our blades decide who is more fit to be general!
刃で決しましょうぞ。
You took the words right out of my mouth.
望むところだ！
（白瑛）
≪一騎打ちなら　勝算はある≫
If it's a one-on-one fight, there's a chance I can beat him!
ドスッ！
（白瑛）ぐはっ！
ははははっ！
信じやがった　バカ女！→
You idiot! You actually believed me!
お前は　なぶり殺しだよ！
I'm going to torture you until you die.
≪もはや　これまでか…≫
Am I going to die?
You think you're so special as the first princess?
何が　第一皇女だ！→
You're nothing! You're worthless!
お前なんざ　ちっぽけな存在よ！
ピィ　ピィ　ピィ　ピィ…
Halharl Infigar!
「灼熱の双掌」！
ドォーーン！
♪♪～
うわっ…。
Kou
♪♪～
Young man... What exactly are you?
（白瑛）少年…　君は一体…。
Me?
僕かい？　僕は…。
I'm...
((そう。　アラジン　お主は…))
That's right, Aladdin, you are a...
♪♪～
マギさ。
I'm a Magi.
A Magi?
マギ…。→
My fan!
扇が…。
おねえさん　ちょっと
それに　触らせてくれないかい？
Miss, could I touch your fan just for a moment?
♪♪～
How are you all doing?
（パイモン）ご機嫌いかが？　皆さん。
私は　パイモン。
I am Paimon.
Created by Solomon as the djinn of maniacal love and chaos.
狭愛と混沌から
ソロモンに造られし　ジンよ。
主は　女王　練白瑛。→
My mistress is Queen Hakuei Ren.
But where did you get the magic to materialize me?
それにしても
私を実体化させるほどの魔力は→
どこから？→
Ah, I spy a Magi.
あ～ら　マギじゃない。
あっ。
♪♪～
Oh goodness, and here is another special sight!
あらまあ！
珍しいお方に会えたわ。　んん～！
♪♪～
This again! I wish I knew what they were saying.
≪まただ。
一体　何を話してるんだろう？≫
I see. I understand the situation.
（パイモン）
なるほど。　事情は分かったわ。→
There are unusual events occurring around the world, aren't there?
世界で
異変が起こっているようね。→
でも　そんなの関係ないわ。
But I don't care about that.
私は　私が王の器と
ほれ込んだ白瑛ちゃんに→
I only care to support my King Candidate, my precious Hakuei.
力を貸すだけ。
そのために　私は　造られたの。
That's why I was created.
King Candidate?
王の器？
（パイモン）そうよ。→
Yes.
My Hakuei is a King Candidate,
chosen by the Magi of the Kou Empire.
白瑛ちゃんだって
王の候補として→
煌帝国のマギに選ばれたんだから。
えっ？
Lord Priest? Where are you?
（銀行屋）神官殿。
どこに　おわすか？　神官殿。→
いや　マギよ。→
Magi!
そこか。→
There you are.
You must not miss your audience with the emperor.
皇帝陛下の拝謁を怠るな。→
怒りに触れるぞ。
He will be angry.
≪（白龍）はっ！　ふっ！
（ジュダル）だって　俺　あの豚野郎→
But I can't stand that pig.
気にくわねぇもん。　白龍！
Hakuryuu!
What is it, Lord Priest?
（白龍）何用か？　神官殿。
（ジュダル）お前が
皇帝になっちまえばいいんだよ。→
Can't you become emperor?
ぱぁ～っと　力を手に入れてさ。
Hurry up and become more powerful already!
迷宮攻略に　行くべきだぜ→
You should go capture a dungeon.
Just like your sister, Hakuei Ren, did.
お前の姉上の練白瑛みてぇにな。
The Lord Priest led me to a dungeon.
（白瑛）私は　その神官に
迷宮へと　いざなわれたのです。
So there are other Magi besides myself.
僕のほかにも　マギがいる。
（パイモン）そうよ。→
That's right.
It is a Magi's duty to select a king.
王の選定こそ　マギの使命。→
あなたは　今まで
王を選んだことはないの？→
Have you not chosen a king yet?
私が　迷宮で
白瑛ちゃんと契約したように。
You know, like how I found Hakuei in that
dungeon and made a contract with her.
あっ。
Oh!
ほんとに　これ　もらっていいの？
Is it really okay for me to take this?
Yeah.
（ドルジ）いいんだ。
ババ様も　きっと喜ぶよ。
I'm sure it's what Elder Baba would've wanted.
うん。
（ボヤン）武器も　持っていけよ。
You should take a weapon with you too!
Silly, Aladdin doesn't need something like that.
（ドルジ）
バ～カ。　アラジンには必要ねぇよ。
あっ！　おにいさん
ゴルタスって人を知ってるかい？
Mister!
Do you know someone named Goltas?
（ドルジ）そんなことが　あったのか。→
That's terrible.
Goltas is a common name among the Kouga people.
「ゴルタス」は
黄牙に　よくある名前なんだ。→
きっと
そいつも　俺たちの家族さ。→
I'm sure he was a member of our family too.
We will pray for his soul.
魂の　弔いをしておくよ。
I see.
そっか…。
（ドルジ）偶然とはいえ→
Thank you for sticking through all of that with us, even though our meeting was just a random coincidence.
最期を見届けてくれて
ありがとうな。
ううん　偶然じゃないよ。
It wasn't a coincidence.
（ドルジ）えっ？
The time has come for you to leave this place.
（ウーゴ）((君は
外へ出るべきときが来たようだ))
♪♪～
Do you remember, Aladdin?
（ウーゴ）
((アラジン　覚えているか？→
You cried about not knowing what you are.
自分が　何者か分からないと
泣いていたことを))
((思いのままに旅をすれば
きっと見つかるよ→
If you travel the world to your heart's content, I am sure you will discover
君の生まれた意味が。→
why you were born into this world.
たくさんの人々と出会い
自分を見つけてゆく。→
May you meet many people and so meet yourself.
That is where your journey will lead you.
そういうふうに
君は　導かれているのだから))
≪本当に　君が
言ってたとおりだね　ウーゴくん≫
It really is just as you said, Ugo.
We're pulling out!
出発するぞ～！→
Has everyone said their goodbyes?
≪兄弟の別れは　済んだか？
See you again, Aladdin.
（ドルジ）アラジン　またな。
（トーヤ）元気でね。
Stay well!
また会おう　黄牙のみんな！
（ドルジ）ああ！
Let's meet again, people of Kouga!
Yeah!
♪♪～
So what happened in Amon's
dungeon was the selection of a king.
≪あの迷宮での出来事が
王を選ぶってことだったんだ≫
≪君に会うことで
何が変わるのかは→
I'm not sure how the future will change now that I've met you,
まだ分からないけど…≫
♪♪～
≪アリババくん
僕は　君に会いに行くよ≫
but I'm going to find you now, Alibaba!
♪♪～
nozoite miyou
Take a look
yubi bouenkyou
through your finger telescope.
me ni mieru sekai ha subete kako no monogatari sa
The world you see before your eyes is a story already told.
♪♪～
kagayaku mirai wo miushinau na yo
Don't lose sight of the bright future ahead.
♪♪～
kimi ni ha motto ippai yume to kibou ga arun da
You're destined to realize great hopes and dreams.
bootto shitetara minogashichau zo
But if you blink for too long, they'll leave you behind.
♪♪～
dekinai riyuu sagasu yori
Instead of searching for an excuse,
yatte mireba ii
why not just give it a try?
♪♪～
nozoite miyou
Take a look
yubi bouenkyou
through your finger telescope.
yubi to yubi wo marume ryoume ni ate
Make circles with your fingers and put them around your eyes.
imeeji shite sagashiteru mono
Picture your hopes and dreams!
♪♪～
atama no naka no adobenchaaa
Picture your personal adventure story!
doko he mukau?
Where are you headed?
yubi bouenkyou
What can you see
♪♪～
yubi no sono sukima ni nani ga mieru?
in the space between your fingers?
tooi you demo hontou ha chikai
It might seem far, but it's really not.
yogen no you na takaramono
It's a promise as valuable as any treasure!
Useless slaves are nothing but food for the desert hyenas!
Don't worry.
I will not let them make you a slave.
Next time: The Battle-Driven Fanalis Tribe.
6th Night
The Battle-Driven Fanalis Tribe
Morgiana, you're so cool!
But wait, when do I get to show up?
（ファティマー）使えない奴隷は
砂漠ハイエナの餌よ！
（モルジアナ）大丈夫。
あなたを　奴隷にはさせません。
（アリババ）モルジアナ　かっけぇ～！
てか…　俺の出番は!?
野田総理は、ＡＳＥＭに出席する
ため
開催国・ラオスに向けて出発した
尖閣諸島をめぐり対立する中国と
の関係改善については、
首脳会談が見送られる一方で、